{
    "available_courses": [
        {
            "course_id": 1,
            "course_name": "C# course",
            "category_type": "basic/intermediate/advance",
            "material": [
                {
                    "material_id": 1,
                    "material_type": "video",
                    "material_media": "http://127.0.0.1:443/api/learningModules/1/video"
                }, 
                {
                    "material_id": 2,
                    "material_type": "image",
                    "material_media": "http://127.0.0.1:443/api/learningModules/2/video"
                }
            ],
            "lectures": [
                {
                    "lectures_id": 1,
                    "lecture_date_and_time": {
                        "@type": "ISODate",
                        "value": "2022-10-31T09:00:00.594Z"
                    },
                    "lectures_type": "unknown"
                }
            ],
            "quiz": [
                {
                    "quiz_id": 1,
                    "description": "tralalalala lores ipstum",
                    "max_tries": 3,
                    "questions": [
                        {
                        "question_number": 1,
                        "question_text": "why do you use C#?",
                        "question_answer_options": {
                            "A": "",
                            "B": "",
                            "C": "",
                            "D": ""
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "question_number": 2,
                        "question_text": "Which on shows the implementation of inheritance?",
                        "question_answer_options": {
                            "A": "",
                            "B": "",
                            "C": "",
                            "D": ""
                        }
                    } ,
                    {
                        "question_number": 2,
                        "question_text": "Which on shows the implementation of inheritance?",
                        "question_answer_options": {
                            "A": "",
                            "B": "",
                            "C": "",
                            "D": ""
                        }
                    }
                    ,
                    {
                        "question_number": 3,
                        "question_text": "Which on shows the implementation of inheritance?",
                        "question_answer_options": {
                            "A": "",
                            "B": "",
                            "C": "",
                            "D": ""
                        }
                    }
                    ,
                    {
                        "question_number": 4,
                        "question_text": "Which on shows the implementation of inheritance?",
                        "question_answer_options": {
                            "A": "",
                            "B": "",
                            "C": "",
                            "D": ""
                        }
                    }
                    ,
                    {
                        "question_number": 5,
                        "question_text": "Which on shows the implementation of inheritance?",
                        "question_answer_options": {
                            "A": "",
                            "B": "",
                            "C": "",
                            "D": ""
                        }
                    }
                    ],
                    "quiz_answers": [
                        {"question_number": 1, "answer": "A"},
                        {"question_number": 2, "answer": "B"},
                        {"question_number": 3, "answer": "D"},
                        {"question_number": 4, "answer": "C"},
                        {"question_number": 5, "answer": "C"}
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "quiz_id": 2
                }

            ]
        },
        {
            "course_id": 2,
            "course_name": "R course",
            "category_type": "basic/intermediate/advance",
            "material": [
                {
                    "material_id": 3,
                    "material_type": "video",
                    "material_media": "http://127.0.0.1:443/api/learningModules/2/video"
                }, 
                {
                    "material_id": 4,
                    "material_type": "video",
                    "material_media": "http://127.0.0.1:443/api/learningModules/2/video"
                }
            ],
            "lectures": [
                {
                    "lectures_id": 2,
                    "lecture_date_and_time": {
                        "@type": "ISODate",
                        "value": "2022-10-31T09:00:00.594Z"
                    },
                    "lectures_type": "unknown"
                }
            ],
            "quiz": {
                "quiz_id": 2,
                "description": "lorem ipsum",
                "max_tries": 3,
                "questions": [
                    {
                    "question_number": 1,
                    "question_text": "why do you use C#?",
                    "question_answer_options": {
                        "A": "",
                        "B": "",
                        "C": "",
                        "D": ""
                    } 
                }, 
                {
                    "question_number": 2,
                    "question_text": "Which on shows the implementation of inheritance?",
                    "question_answer_options": {
                        "A": "",
                        "B": "",
                        "C": "",
                        "D": ""
                    }
                } , 
                {
                    "question_number": 2,
                    "question_text": "Which on shows the implementation of inheritance?",
                    "question_answer_options": {
                        "A": "",
                        "B": "",
                        "C": "",
                        "D": ""
                    }
                }
                , 
                {
                    "question_number": 3,
                    "question_text": "Which on shows the implementation of inheritance?",
                    "question_answer_options": {
                        "A": "",
                        "B": "",
                        "C": "",
                        "D": ""
                    }
                }
                ,
                {
                    "question_number": 4,
                    "question_text": "Which on shows the implementation of inheritance?",
                    "question_answer_options": {
                        "A": "",
                        "B": "",
                        "C": "",
                        "D": ""
                    }
                }
                ,
                {
                    "question_number": 5,
                    "question_text": "Which on shows the implementation of inheritance?",
                    "question_answer_options": {
                        "A": "",
                        "B": "",
                        "C": "",
                        "D": ""
                    }
                }
                ],
                "quiz_answers": [
                    {"question_number": 1, "answer": "A"},
                    {"question_number": 2, "answer": "B"},
                    {"question_number": 3, "answer": "D"},
                    {"question_number": 4, "answer": "C"},
                    {"question_number": 5, "answer": "C"}
                ]
            } 
        }

    ],
    "user_register_to_courses" : [
        {
            "user_id":1,
            "course_id": 1,
            "quiz_submission": [
                {
                    "quiz_submission_no": 1,
                    "quiz_id": 1,
                    "grade": "A",
                    "grade_details": "it was perfect. no more comment.",
                    "status": "pass",
                    "rating": 10,
                    "feedback": "you have passed all quizes question flawlessly. You are as good as Steve Jobs."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "user_id":2,
            "course_id": 1,
            "quiz_submission": [
                {
                    "quiz_submission_no": 2,
                    "quiz_id": 1,
                    "grade": "F",
                    "grade_details": "Please study harder. You only have one correct answer per 10 questions",
                    "status": "not pass",
                    "rating": 2,
                    "feedback": "Sorry. You need to study more."
                },
                {
                    "quiz_submission_no": 3,
                    "quiz_id": 1,
                    "grade": "B",
                    "grade_details": "Great progess!",
                    "status": "pass",
                    "rating": 8,
                    "feedback": "You study hard for the second quiz! good improvement."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "user_id":1,
            "course_id": 2,
            "quiz_submission": [ ]
        }
    ]
}